Where hope goes to die.
The Abandoned is a thriller, horror, mystery film directed by Eytan Rockaway.
A troubled young woman who, in a last-ditch effort at getting her life together, takes a job
working nights as a security guard at an abandoned luxury apartment building.
Stuck with a brusque rent-a-cop as her partner, she tries to not let her
mind play tricks on her while she patrols the empty halls.
But as the night progresses strange things begin to happen -
and she realizes it may not all be in her head.
Cooper, played by Jason Patric.
Streak, played by Louisa Krause.
Jim, played by Mark Margolis.
Martin Rollins, played by Carlos Velazquez.
Dixon, played by Ezra Knight.
The Abandoned (also known as The Confines, and Confined) is a 2015 American
supernatural horror film directed by Eytan Rockaway, and written by Ido Fluk.
It stars Jason Patric, Louisa Krause and Mark Margolis.
The film premiered at the Los Angeles Film Festival on June 14, 2015, and was
released in theaters and video on demand on January 8, 2016 by IFC Films.
The film concerns a struggling young woman, who tries to reacquire her normal life by
taking a job as a security guard at an abandoned apartment building.
The Abandoned marked Rockaway's debut as director.
The tone is mind_bending and dark and intense.